DAVID SHIN

347-803-0075

davidshin@ac.c4q.nyc

ŵ davidsh.in | inkedin.com/in/y-davidshin | inkedin.com/davidyshin

Skills

JavaScript | ES6 | HTML5 | CSS3 | React | Node | Git | Express | Restful API

Projects & Freelance

Star-Fall - starfall.netlify.com - github.com/davidyshin/starfall (Javascript, p5.js)

- A fast paced star-shooter game inspired by the popular 80's arcade game Galaga. Uses ES6 syntax JavaScript and the p5.js/p5.play libraries. p5.js is used for HTML5 canvas rendering and p5.play deals with the sprite class and handles collision detection.

Elevate - <u>www.elevate.careers</u> - <u>github.com/davidyshin/elevate</u> (Javascript, React)

 Worked on a 4 person team to design and create a full stack web application built to assist and motivate users in their job search process. Provides features such as a notification reminders, an upload system using Amazon Web Services, and a user incentive system with experience points. Uses ES6 Syntax Javascript, React, CSS.

VACCess NYC - https://vaccessnyc.netlify.com - github.com/davidyshin/vaccessnyc (Javascript, React)

Application that helps local New Yorkers find flu vaccination centers near them using the OpenDataNYC
Api. Built using HTML/CSS, Javascript, React.js, and the Google-Map-React NPM module.

Education

C4Q (Coalition 4 Queens), Long Island City

Full Stack Web Development Fellowship (Expected Graduation May 2018)

- Enrolled in an intensive 9-month project-based full stack web-development curriculum designed by engineers from Vice, Facebook, Yahoo, Artsy, and LinkedIn. Topics include Node, Express, React/Redux, PostgreSQL, Git/GitHub, TDD, Algorithms, APIs.

Experience

TD Bank

Teller I — February 2017 - August 2017

 Provided quality customer service; Took care of customer transactions, providing personalized banking advice. Demonstrated money management skills by taking care of the cash boxes and machines.

The Good Neighbor Community Church

Youth Pastor — September 2015 - August 2017

Coordinated all ministries pertaining to teenagers ages 14-18, developing a curriculum and delivering an original lesson every week. Developed and operated the youth ministry's budget, enabling coordination of events and community service activities.

Delivery.com LLC

Customer Service Representative — November 2014 - May 2015

- Managed relations with laundry/dry cleaning merchants and clients via phone and email. Gained firsthand consumer front-end experience, and worked with web-development team through Jira.